trevvy.com 2014-12-17

# Trevvy | Privacy

**This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.trevvy.com**

**Information Collection and Use**  
Trevvy.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Trevvy.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Registration**  
When you register with us, we will ask for your email address, date of birth and location. Upon registration and signing into our services, you are no longer anonymous to us. Trevvy.com is the sole owner of the information collected on the site and none of your information will be distributed to any other party. The same applies to newsletter subscriptions.

**Cookies & Logfiles**  
Trevvy.com may set and access its cookies on your computer. However, such is in no way linked to any personal identifiable information while you are on our site. IP addresses are used to analyse trends, track users' movements and administer the site. They are also used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and are in no way linked to any personal identifiable information.

**Third Party Web Analytics**  
A third party web analytic and site census service provided by a reputable vendor may be in used on Trevvy.com. The service does not gather any personally identifiable information and its sole purpose is to measure traffic movements, trends and aggregate demographics of our users.

**External Links**  
This privacy policy is only applicable to Trevvy.com. Though it contains links to other sites, Trevvy.com will not be responsible for the privacy practices of the externally linked sites. Users are encouraged to note the privacy statements of said sites when personal information is collected.

**Surveys, Contests and Polls**  
Participation in surveys, contests and polls in Trevvy.com is strictly voluntary. Specific information may be requested when the need arises; hence, users are not obliged to disclose information if uncomfortable. Specific information includes contact number, email address and demographic information (such as occupation and age). Information is solely owned by Trevvy.com and will not be distributed to other parties.

**Referral**  
Should the user refer a friend to Trevvy.com, only the name and email address will be requested with the sole purpose of sending a one-time email invitation to visit the site. The referee may contact the webmaster of Trevvy.com to have the information removed from the database.

**Hotbods, Classifieds & Forums**  
Users of Trevvy Hotbods, Classifieds and Forums are to note that these sections are public and readable. There are options available for users to make use of these areas without publicly disclosing their email addresses or any such personal information. However, Trevvy.com has no control over spammers harvesting names, emails and other information if users choose to reveal such information in their advertisements or postings.

**Profiles**  
Members looking below the age of 18 may be emailed for age verification. The user will be then be required to email a photograph identification such as national registration identification card, driver's license, passport or any form of photo identification documents which contains information of the user's name, photograph and date of birth. Upon verification, the information will be destroyed, and will not be passed on to any third party.

**Security**  
This website will take every precaution to protect its users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, this information is protected both online and offline. SSL encryption or other similar encryption methods will be used to protect sensitive information revealed in the process of taking purchase orders online.

**Mailing Lists**  
Users may be automatically subscribed to all newsletters and mailing lists they are eligible for on Trevvy.com. All users have a choice to opt out from these mailing lists through their personal control settings or by contacting our customer service staff. Mailing lists are not sold to any third party and are only used strictly for the intended informational purposes. In addition, Trevvy.com may inform all its registered users of site and service changes or other important announcements. Members may not unsubscribe from service announcements without also terminating your account.

**Account**  
Termination  
Users who wish to terminate their account on Trevvy.com may do so by contacting our customer service staff. Upon confirmation of termination, your account will be removed within three working days. Trevvy.com retains the right to record your personal information even after the termination of your account whether it is terminated at our discretion or your request if we have reasons to believe that Trevvy.com may be required to produce such information in a court of law or at the request of relevant authorities as a result of your actions on the website including, but not limited to, libel, defamation, spam or sale of illegal drugs.

Correction/Updating Personal Information  
If a user's personal identifiable information changes (such as occupation), or if a user no longer desires the services provided by Trevvy.com, the administer will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove the user's personal data provided to the management. This may be done at the member information page or via email to the site's webmaster.  
Notification of Changes  
If Trevvy.com should so decide to amend its privacy policy, the published Privacy Statement will be updated. Users are advised to check this page for updates in information that is collected and its usage.  
Disclaimers  
You agree that your use of Trevvy.com shall be at your sole risk to the fullest extent permitted by law; Trevvy.com, its management (staff, employees) disclaim all warranties, express or implied, in connection with the website and your use thereof.

Trevvy makes no warranties or representations about the accuracy or completeness off this site's content, or the content of any sites linked to this site, and assumes no liability or responsibility for any of the following:

(i) errors, mistakes, or inaccuracies of content  
(ii) any interruption or cessation of transmission to or from our website  
(iii) any bugs, viruses, trojan horses, or the like which may be transmitted to or through the website by any third party, and/or any errors or omissions in any content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any content posted, email transmitted, or otherwise made available via Trevvy.com.  
(iv) Trevvy.com does not warrant, endorse, guarantee, or assume responsibility for any product or service advertised or featured in any banner or other form of advertising. Trevvy.com will not be a party to or in any way be held responsible for monitoring any transaction(s) between you and third-party providers of products or services as with the purchase of a product or service through any medium or in any environment. You should use your best judgment and exercise caution where appropriate.

This policy is correct as at 1 May 2011.
